For the game Mount & Blade Warband, there is a Game of Thrones mod
And before you ask: no, it does not have incest
Why the modders ignored the most important part of Game of Thrones, I don't know
My favorite thing is the unpredictability, like how they killed off the main character
He was always a good guy, always giving out advice, and then they killed him like that
On the toilet
This mod takes place during the second book so Tywin is still alive
And today we're going to help him take over the seven kingdoms
Obviously, first he needs to hire us
Ok, he's got a soldier job open, 90 coins a week
That's like the price of cheese
So I'm risking my life for cheddar
Worth it!
You will be equipped as befits your rank, what does that mean?
Well, as you can see, everyone else has horses and armor, and he gave me a stick
I'm beginning to think this Tywin guy might actually be a dick
Alright, he said room for promotion so maybe I'm being greedy
I have been in Tywin's army for three years now, and he's given me fuckall
I've had it, I'm revolting against the Lannisters, who's with me?!?
Their army has 2080 soldiers and we have...
the one
So it's pretty even
Maybe I underestimated my opponents, and that day I found out what the inside of a Lannister prison cell looked like
I escaped, and now I have a new goal
To take the capital King's landing for myself, but to do that I need help from the king in the North
Robb Stark is much nicer than Tywin
He gave me two sticks!
After a couple of battles I don't consider Robb to be my king anymore
I consider him to be my friend
"We are going to a wedding, we have a friend that needs a date"
Alright, free food!
"Can you look after my wolf?"
Screw you Robb! Take the dog to the wedding!
And while you're there, I am taking your house
With an army of... 16 farmers
The castle is mine, Winterfell has been besieged by Torghen Flint
This might be a problem
And that was when I found out what the inside of a northern prison cell looks like!
I lost the castle and I can't take my revenge because Robb Stark is...
Digesting arrow heads, but this gives me the chance to give Westeros to the one true king
Renly Baratheon?
Oh, he is the guy with the hot wife, and he is an ultra arch-homosexual
That means she is single!!! (:
In the Middle Ages, soldiers were actually encouraged to hit on their king's wife
Hey Margaery, are you from Tennesee? Because you are the only Ten I've...
And that's how I found out prison cell...
I'm a medieval Houdini, and this time I can take my revenge!
By joining his brother Stannis and his crazy cult
Stannis says he is not even going to give me an interview
What do you mean I've had too many recent employers!?!
Fuck you Stannis, you Manson ass... Oh oh
No, not this time, motherfucker, eat a stick!
I hate these places
I could ride south and join Dorne and fight with Oberyn Martell
No, he doesn't seem very HEADstrong...
I think his opponents might get aHEAD of him
Also he is a pervert.
That leaves me with eh... Nothing
Why do the seven kingdoms only have five kingdoms?
I guess I'm going to take King's Landing alone!
Yeahhhhhhh
Nope, nope, no, nope, terrible idea, no
Maybe I should give up... No, there is one more thing that can help me
That's so far away though, but I guess I have no other choice
I need Aragorn and the riders of Rohan!
(Just some tourist videos from New Zealand)
Yeahhhh
Death to lions; glory to red pandas!
King's Landing is mine! I shall take it back to a simpler time, a better time.
When King's Landing was still called: King's Still In-Flight